

ANISHA KHAREL Graphics Designer

About me

I am an ambitious and hardworking individual. I am adept at handling multiple tasks on a daily basis competently and at working well under pressure. My key strength is communication, and building strong relationships with people in order to deliver the best results.

Contact

9862560590

ansukharel456@gmail.com

Butwal

Education

2021-Present

Bachelor's Degree on Electronics Communication and Information Engineering from Paschimanchal Campus

2019-2020

+2 Technical Science from Kalika Manavgyan Secondary School

2017-2018

SEE from Kalika Manavgyan Secondary School

Experience

2021-Present

Graphics Designer Innovative Computer Engineering Students' Society ,WRC

2023-Present

Freelance Graphics Designer
Damsole Technologies

Other Experience

2023

Mentoring a Figma's Session.

Tools

FIGMA

PHOTOSHOP

ILLUSTRATOR

MS-OFFICE

CANVA

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs etc.

My Recent Works







Certifactes and Appreciation







Social Profiles & Portfolios

Behance: https://www.behance.net/anysa-kharel

Github: https://github.com/anysa-kharel

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anisha-kharel-502207244/